boxbe.com 2013-06-30

# Boxbe: Privacy Policy

**Last updated on November 23, 2011**

Boxbe takes the privacy of our members seriously, and recognizes that doing so is critical to the success of our business. Boxbe has made and will continue to make significant efforts to protect the identity and personal information of our members.

This Privacy Policy explains how Boxbe collects, stores, protects and uses the information you provide or grant access to when you use Boxbe's services. It also explains how you can control the collection, correction and or deletion of information.

If this policy is updated, a notice will appear on your Boxbe Dashboard page and remain there for a minimum of 30 days or until you delete it. You agree to regularly check your Boxbe Dashboard. Boxbe and you are both subject to the terms of this privacy policy as part of the Terms of Service whether or not you have read the latest version. Please email [privacy@boxbe.com](mailto:privacy@boxbe.com) with any questions or suggestions.

For practical tips from the federal government and technology industry to help you guard against Internet fraud and protect your personal information and computer, go to [OnGuard Online's website]().

### Information Collection and Use

  _Account Information_

To establish your account with Boxbe, you are asked to provide personal information for registration, including your name, and email address. Boxbe requires your email address and the other personal information and preferences you are required to provide during the signup process to provide Boxbe's services to you, to communicate with you and to otherwise help improve the quality of the messages you receive. If you do not wish to share such information with Boxbe, your sole remedy is to not receive Boxbe's services. During the customization process of Boxbe's services, you may in your discretion elect to submit additional personal information that will be used to improve the quality of messages you receive and Boxbe's services. 

  _Access Credentials_

In order for Boxbe to have programmatic access to your enrolled email accounts, a requirement for many of Boxbe's service functions, Boxbe collects from you and maintains certain authentication and authorization information ("Access Credentials"), which may include email addresses and passwords. Boxbe maintains these Access Credentials using industry standard security practices.

  _Message Content, Your Policy Data_

Boxbe collects and uses some or all of the email messages in your enrolled accounts. Boxbe also stores and provides tools for you to maintain your guest list and other data related to your account in order to provide Boxbe's services to you. 

Boxbe uses such email messages and information to provide you with our products and services, to improve these services, to contact you, to notify senders that you are using Boxbe to screen your mail, to conduct market research, and to produce and maintain aggregate statistics and provide market data services. 

Boxbe pays for and profits from its services by, among other things, aggregating and analyzing anonymized data that is collected by the Boxbe service from commercial emails (e.g. messages from businesses seeking a customer relationship with you and messages from businesses with wihich you have already established a relationship, including purchase confirmations) in enrolled accounts, including your enrolled email accounts. By using Boxbe's services, you authorize Boxbe to collect, analyze, aggregate, and retain data derived from such email messages you receive.

Boxbe will not sell, rent or share personally identifiable information about you to other parties except to provide the services you've requested or when we have your explicit permission, or when: 

  * We provide information to trusted partners who work with Boxbe under confidentiality agreements
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or to establish or exercise our legal rights to defend against legal claims
  * We believe it is necessary to share information to investigate or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud to other Boxbe or email users, or to violations of Boxbe's Terms of Service, or as required by law; and/or 
  * We transfer information about you if Boxbe is acquired by or merged with another company. 

  _Website_

When you use Boxbe's website (www.boxbe.com), we collect information about your usage of Boxbe: 

  * Your browser transmits information in its requests when you access web pages. Boxbe's servers record some of that information which can include IP address, browser type, referring and exit pages and URLs, pages viewed and other such information
  * Boxbe records what kind of operating system you have so that Boxbe can deliver the appropriate software and services to help you manage your email.

### Email Modification, Annotations

When you send email, Boxbe does not change, alter the content or delete information from your email messages in any way. As with other email services, we may annotate the routing information to ensure proper delivery.

In some situations Boxbe adds information to the top of emails you receive. This added information alerts you so you can decide and indicate to Boxbe how you want similar messages to be handled in the future, and whether to add the sender to your priority guest list.

### Communication

By agreeing to our Terms of Service during registration, you agree to receive messages such as newsletters, notices about changes or improvements to Boxbe's services or other Boxbe information. You can opt out of certain emails from your Account Info page.

### Confidentiality and Security

Except as provided otherwise in this Privacy Policy, Boxbe limits access to personal information about you to Boxbe employees and independent contractors who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products, services or customer support to you in order to do their jobs.

Computer, physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations are used to protect personal information about you that you share with Boxbe.

### Children

You are not permitted to register for or use any of Boxbe's services if you are under the age of 13 or if you are under the age of 18 and your parent or legal guardian has not reviewed and agreed to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service on your behalf. Protecting the privacy of young children is a priority. Boxbe does not solicit or knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allows them to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you have reason to believe that Boxbe might have any information from or about a child under 13, please email us at [privacy@boxbe.com](mailto:privacy@boxbe.com).

### Links

When you use a link to go from our website to another website, Boxbe's Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Boxbe is not responsible for the practices employed by other websites linked to or from our website. These links are provided solely as pointers on topics that may be useful to Boxbe members.

### Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website or company, or you wish to correct or delete any incorrect personal information, please contact us at [privacy@boxbe.com](mailto:privacy@boxbe.com), or send mail to:

Boxbe, Inc.  
65 Broadway, Suite 601  
New York, NY 10006
